Florence Rena Sabin Papers 1916-1973 Mss.B.Sa12
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence (Box 1-39)
  - Johns Hopkins Press, 1921, 1931-38
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1923-35
  - Johns Hopkins University - Appointments, 1916-17
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1935-36
  - Johnson, Treat B, 1926-31
  - Johnston, Paul N, 1936
  - Joyner, Austin L, 1931-45
  - K, 1923-44
  - Kagan, B M, 1943
  - Kahn, Morton C, 1931-32
  - Kahn, Reuben L, 1930-33
  - Kaiden-Kazanjian Studios, Inc., 1933-40
  - Kalkstein, David, 1933
  - Kanazawa Iryokikai Company, 1938
  - Kanof, Abram, 1928
  - Kaplan, Sisters M & R, 1932
  - Kastlin, George J, 1938
  - Kastor, Robert, 1930
  - Keibel-Mall Embryology, 1907-11
  - Keith, Sir Arthur, 1934
  - Keller, Helen, 1922
  - Kelly, Howard A, 1931-35
  - Kelly, Hugh J, 1938
  - Kendall, S, 1923
  - Keniston, Maria Renza, 1936
  - Kennedy, Foster, 1930
  - Kennedy, John W, 1936
  - Kennedy, Marie, 1938
  - Kenyon, Fanny H, 1929
  - Key, J Albert, 1921-31
  - Kieran, James M, 1932
  - Kiev Scientific Research Institute of Tuberculosis, 1939
  - Kilgore, Mrs. J D, 1937
  - Killiam, Mrs. George W, 1939
  - Kindwallm Josef A, 1923-40
  - Kinghorn, Hugh M, 1933
  - Kinsley, Prudence Ellis, 1937
  - Kirkbride, Elizabeth B, 1934
  - Klemperer, Paul, 1930
  - Klotz, Oskar, 1933
  - Knisely, Melvin H, 1936-37
  - Knopf, Mrs. S. Adolphus, 1929-42
  - Knouf, Clyde E, 1932
  - Knower, Henry McElderry, 1924-39
  - Knox, Helen, 1928
  - Knuckles, A J, 1932-33
  - Koenig, Hedwig, 1932
  - Konzelman, F W, 1933
  - Kosofsky, Isidore, 1938
  - Kotschnig, Walter, 1936
  - Kover, Mrs. Sidney J, 1939
  - Krafka, Joseph, Jr., 1930
  - Kramer, Benjamin, 1930
  - Kraul, Ludwig, 1929
  - Krause, Allen K, 1929-35
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B, 1926-31
  - Kubie, David S, 1928
  - Kubie, Lawrence S, 1925-44
  - Kubie, Mrs. Susan H, 1936
  - Kugelmass, I Newton, 1927-34
  - Kuhn, Irene, 1937-38
  - Kuitert, J H, 1936
  - Kumpf, Katharine F, 1931
  - Kunde, M M, 1932
  - Kuttner, Ann G, 1936-37
  - L, 1920-37, n.d.
  - Laidlaw, R W, 1933
  - La Master, Fay, 1934-35
  - Lamb, Frederick H, 1932
  - Lambert, Samuel W, 1934
  - Lang, Wilbert J, 1909, 1937
  - Lange, Mathilde M, 1939
  - Langeluttig, Elisabeth, 1936
  - Langworthy, Orthello R, 1926-34
  - Lapham, Mary E, 1932
  - Laughton, J R C, 1933
  - Laughton, Mrs. N C, 1933
  - Lawrence, John S, 1930-32
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1930, 1942
  - Leadership Institute Inc., 1935-40
  - League of Nations Association, 1934
  - Leake, Chauncy Depew, 1924-25
  - Lee, Ferdinand C, 1929
  - Leffler, J Dean, 1935
  - Lehndorff, Heinrich, 1940
  - Leitheiser, Margaret A, 1939
  - Le Page, Samuel M, 1931
  - L'Esperance Elise S, 1929-37
  - Levene, Phoebus Aaron, 1931-38
  - Leverock, Pearl, 1935
  - Levy, Robert L, 1923, 1932
  - Lewis, Frederick Thomas, 1918-39
  - Lewis, Marian, 1936
  - Lewis, Paul Aden, 1924-28
  - Lewis, Warren H, 1928
  - Lewis, Wilfrid J, 1943
  - Lewiton, Mina, 1936
  - Libby, Frederick J, 1926
  - Libman, E, 1930
  - Lichtmann, Sina, 1934
  - Liebaner, Eugenia, 1932
  - Lilly, Lillian A, 1932
  - Lilly Research Laboratories, 1932-35
  - Lindsay, L Seton, 1933
  - Lipp, C C, 1924
  - Lippincott, J. B. & Company, 1939
  - List of Early Medical Journals, n.d.
  - List of Three Carnegie Reprints, 1923-32
  - Literature Lists, n.d.
  - Litterer, William, 1929
  - Little, C C, 1926-29
  - Livingston, Burton Edward Opitz, 1929-36
  - Locy, J W, 1924
  - Loeb, Robert F, 1933-38
  - Login, B. & Son, Incorporated, 1933-36
  - Long, Esmond R, 1925-46
  - Long, Perrin H, 1933
  - Long Island Biological Association, 1936
  - Longcope, Warfield T, 1929-37
  - Loranz, C P, 1940
  - Lord Baltimore Press, 1935
  - Losee, J R, 1928
  - Lowe, Ardith, 1937
  - Lucke, Baldwin, 1922-36
  - Ludeman, Clifford G, 1930-32
  - Lübeck, Germany, Disaster, 1931
  - Lurie, Max B, 1932-35
  - Lusk, Graham, 1923, 1932
  - Lyman, David Russell, 1932, 1938
  - Lyons, Arthur, 1925
  - M, 1926-44
  - Mc, 1923-30
  - Maass and Davidson, 1933
  - Macallum, Archibald Byron, 1928-30
  - MacCullam, W G, 1922, 1929
  - MacDonald, Claudine, 1934
  - MacFarlane, Catharine, 1936
  - MacInnes, Duncan Arthur, 1938-41
  - MacKenzie, A Stanley, 1923
  - MacKlin, Charles C, 1926-36
  - MacKlin, Madge Thurlow, 1930
  - MacLeod, Christine C, 1932
  - MacLeod, Colin Munro, 1939
  - MacLeod, John James Rickard, 1937
  - MacNeal, Ward J, 1927-32
  - Mahon, Grace, 1939-40
  - Malins, Margery M, 1933
  - Mall, Daniel, 1933-35
  - Mall, F. P., Biography - Letters, n.d.
  - Mall, F. P., Biography - Notes, n.d.
  - Mall, F. P. - Book Review, n.d.
  - Mall, Franklin Paine (New Data), n.d.
  - Mall Portrait Fund
  - Malloch, Archibald, 1932-33
  - Mallon, Angela M, 1934
  - Mallon, Winifred, 1938
  - Mallory, Frank B, 1933
  - Maltby, Margaret E, 1917
  - Man, Evelyn B, 1934
  - Mansfield, Ivan, 1936
  - Marks, Nedah E, 1937
  - Marlow, Arthur, 1929
  - Martin, Alexander T, 1935
  - Martin, Walter B, 1920
  - Mast, Louise R, 1932
  - Mathews, Lois Kimball, 1918
  - Mayer, Edgar, 1935
  - Mayo, Katherine, 1936-37
  - Mayo, William J, 1932
  - Mazur, John F, 1936-37
  - McAlpin, K R, 1930
  - McBroom, Russell E, 1940
  - McCann, William S, 1925
  - McCartie, D B, 1937
  - McClung, Clarence Erwin, 1927-37
  - McClure, Roy D, 1911-37
  - McCollum, Emabel, 1927
  - McCollum, E V, 1923-25
  - McCoy, G W, 1933
  - McDonald, Ellice, 1931
  - McEwen, Currier, 1933-40
  - McFadyen, Aubrey D, 1936
  - McFarlane, W D, 1929
  - McGorkey, Mary L, 1937
  - McGraw, Arthur B, 1935-36
  - McHale, Kathryn, 1934
  - McIntosh, Rustin, 1931
  - McJunkin, F A, 1918
  - McKay, J A, 1936
  - McKee, Thistle M, 1933
  - McKinley, Earl B, 1934
  - McLean, A J, 1922-30
  - McLean, Jay, 1940-41
  - McLean, R K, 1942
  - Mead, Kate Campbell - Hurd, 1933-40
  - Mealing, H G, 1925
  - Meanes, Lenna L, 1925
  - Medearis, Donald N, 1928
  - Medical Aid to China and Spain, 1937-40
  - Medical Woman's Journal, 1935-40
  - Medical Women's National Association, 1935
  - Medlar, E M, 1927-38
  - Meleney, Frank Lamont, 1934
  - Meleney, Henry E, 1922-25
  - Mellon, Ralph R, 1931
  - Mellus, E Lindon, 1920
  - Menten, Maud L, 1931
  - Menzel, A E O, 1935-36
  - Mercer, Samuel T, 1923-25
  - Merck and Company, Incorporated, 1933
  - Messina, Giovanna C, 1934
  - Metcalf, Kenneth M, 1935
  - Metcalf, Maynard, 1922-27
  - Metzelthin, Pearl V, 1936
  - Meyer, Arthur W, 1932-34
  - Meyer, Leo, 1938
  - Meyer, Rose D, 1932
  - Meyers, Mary A, 1934
  - Michaelis, Leonor, 1945
  - Michels, N A, 1931
  - Microscopes, n.d.
  - Microtome, 1934
  - Milk Consumption Statistics, 1923-34
  - Miller, Alberta, 1934
  - Miller, Benjamin F, 1938
  - Miller, David K, 1939, n.d.
  - Miller, Franklin R, 1931-45
  - Miller, Franklin R. - Article in Science, 1931-32
  - Miller, J Hillis, 1938-39
  - Miller, James A, 1931
  - Miller, William Snow, 1919-36
  - Millwee, Robert H, 1926
  - Minot, Charles Sedgwick, 1912
  - Minot, George Richards, 1923-36
  - Mirman, Joseph M, 1934
  - Missouri Public Schools, 1935
  - Mitchell, A Graeme, 1927
  - Mohler, Mrs. William, 1930
  - Montgomery, Clare, 1936-37
  - Montgomery, M Laurence, 1934
  - Morgan, Agnes Fay, 1937
  - Morgan, Ann, 1926-32
  - Morgan, Arthur E, 1922
  - Morgan, Ruth, 1933
  - Morrey, Charles B, 1931-32
  - Morris, Esther Z, 1933
  - Morris, W H, 1925, n.d.
  - Morton, John J, 1921, 1938
  - Moses, Gertrude, 1928
  - Moses, Jacob M, 1933
  - Mosher, Edná, 1938
  - Moulton, F R, 1937-38
  - Moulton, Gertrude E, 1937
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1927-37
  - Muir, E, 1936
  - Muir, Robert, 1925
  - Muller, Gulli Lindh, 1925-37
  - Mullin, W V, 1933
  - Mumford, Edward W, 1937
  - Murphy, James B, 1921-22, 1942
  - Murphy, John F, 1935
  - Murray, Thomas F., Jr., 1932
  - Museum of Natural History, 1935
  - Myers, B D, 1933
  - Myers, C, 1927
  - Myers, J L, 1932
  - N, 1927-40
  - Nagayo, M, 1923
  - Naples Table Association - Correspondence, 1915-33
  - Naples Table Association - General Committees, Minutes, 1915-31
  - Naples Table Association - Ellen Richards Research Prize, Printed material, 1924, n.d.
  - Naples Table Association - Ellen Richards Research Prize, Applications, 1919-24
  - Nash, Mrs. Jessie R, 1926, 1939-41
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1925-38
  - National Academy of Sciences - Abstract of Papers, Annual Meeting, 1938
  - National Achievement Award, 1932-37
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association, 1937
  - National Council of Women, 1932-38
  - National Economy League, 1935
  - National Geographic Society, 1924
  - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1931
  - National Research Council, 1944
  - National Research Council - Executive Board, 1931-33
  - National Travel Club, 1930-37
  - National Tuberculosis Association, 1926-37
  - National Tuberculosis Association - Committee on Medical Research, 1928-44
  - National Tuberculosis Association Meeting, Toronto, June 1933
  - National Tuberculosis Association Meeting - Abstracts of Papers, n.d.
  - Nebel, Bernard R, 1933
  - Négre, L, 1937
  - Neilson, W A, 1935-36
  - Nelson, Josephine, 1936
  - Neuenschwander, Nelly, 1924
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1929-1938, n.d.
  - New York Hospital, 1936
  - New York Infirmary for Women and Children, 1933
  - New York Museum of Science and Industry, 1936
  - New York Times, 1937
  - New York University, 1932-37
  - Newburger, Bernard, 1933-34
  - Newcomb, C F, 1937
  - Newell, A G, 1939
  - Nicolson, Marjorie H, 1940
  - Niemeyer, Marie, 1938
  - Nisbet, Mrs. James Douglas, 1939
  - Nishibe, M, 1927
  - Nobel, G Kingsley, 1928
  - Nobel, Centennial Committee, 1933
  - Nobel Prize, 1931-39, n.d.
  - Noether, Emmy, Memorial Fund - A to Z
  - Noether, Emmy, Memorial Fund Reports
  - Norlin, George, 1936-39
  - Norton, V V, 1934
  - O, 1928-39
  - Oberlin College, 1937
  - O'Brien, Daniel P, 1930-32
  - Ogden, Esther G, 1935-36
  - Oglethorpe University, 1935
  - Oliver, Jean, 1931, 1940
  - Opie, Eugene Lindsay, 1933-38
  - Oppenheimer, Ella, 1920-22
  - Ordway, Thomas, 1932
  - Ordway, William H, 1937
  - Osgood, Edwin E, 1937
  - Osler, Sir William, 1901, 1920-26
  - Osterhout, Winthrop John Vanheuven, 1929-32
  - Ott, H N, 1927-33
  - Owens, William A, 1936-37
  - Owings, James C, 1934
  - P, 1921-40
  - Page, Irvine Hemly, 1931-36
  - Palmer, Edward, 1931
  - Palmer, George T, 1935
  - Palmer, Sarah E, 1935-36
  - Parfitt, C D, 1933
  - Park, Edwards A, 1923-39
  - Park, Marion Edwards, 1928-41
  - Park, William H, 1930-34
  - Parker, Barbara Ann, 1936
  - Parry, Gertrude Hoyt, 1933
  - Parsons, Lawrence, 1930
  - Parsons, Susanne R, 1928-32
  - Partridge, Emma Dot, 1935-36
  - Pascher, Frances, 1939
  - Patron, F Margaret, 1940
  - Patras, Mary C, 1937
  - Patten, Bradley M, 1933-35
  - Patterson, Mrs. Andrew J, 1936
  - Patterson, Minnie, 1936
  - Patton, Mrs. R C, 1936
  - Peabody, Francis W, 1926
  - Pearce, Louise, 1936-43
  - Pearce, Richard Mills, 1924-27
  - Pearse, Herman E, 1936
  - Peebles, Florence, 1934
  - Peirce, Ethel Girwood, 1923-26
  - Peking Union Medical College, 1921-30
  - Pen and Brush Club, 1937
  - Pender, H L, 1927
  - Pendleton, Ellen F, 1928
  - Pennell, S, 1936
  - Pepper, Annie M, 1923
  - Pernicious Anemia, 1926-31
  - Peters, LeRoy S, 1933
  - Petroff, S A, 1929-31
  - Petrunkevitch, Alexander, 1923-34
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1935
  - Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra of New York, 1930-34
  - Phillips, H A, 1930
  - Photographs, n.d.
  - Physiological Reviews, 1928, 1935
  - Pictorial Review Prize, 1929-32
  - Pierce, Mila I, 1932
  - Piney, A, 1924-27
  - Pinkerton, Elizabeth, 1937
  - Pinner, Max, 1926-39
  - Pisko, Mrs. S, 1931-32
  - Pitts, Juanita, 1945
  - Place, P O, 1934
  - Plagens, George M, 1930
  - Plaggemeyer, H W, 1922
  - Pholman, Augustus Grote, 1923, 1935
  - Polayes, S H, 1936
  - Pompeian Corporation, 1929
  - Pond, Samuel E, 1940
  - Portland, Maine. Evening News, 1931
  - Pottenger, F M, 1929-30
  - Powers, Grover F, 1929-34
  - Powers, John H, 1933
  - Pratt, Elsie Seelye, 1926-27
  - Pratt, Frances J, 1930-35
  - Pratt, Trude, 1940
  - Price, Benjamin, 1930
  - Pritchett, Edith, 1934
  - Pritchett, Henry S, 1935
  - Pritchett, Ida W, 1933-35
  - Public Health Association of New York City, 1938
  - Public Opinion Company, (Wilson College), 1933
  - Purdy, Ann P, 1925, 1933
  - Putnam, Irma Kellers, 1922-24
  - Pyle, David H McAlpin, 1937
  - Quinn, Lawrence, 1932
  - R, 1929-38
  - Rader, Mrs. R, 1934
  - Radium, Correspondence Concerning, 1926, 1932
  - Ralli, Elaine P, 1934-36
  - Ransom, Stephen Walter - Biography, 1942 -45, n.d.
  - Reed, C I, 1926
  - Reed, G B, 1933
  - Rees, Charles W, 1935-36
  - Rees, Maurice H, 1936-38
  - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, 1937
  - Reich, Carl, 1932
  - Reichel, John, 1928-39
  - Reid, Helen Rogers, 1932, 1936
  - Reimer, Marie, 1933
  - Renfrew, Alice G, 1927-40
  - Reprints - Acknowledgments of, 1914-35
  - Requests for Reprints
  - Research
  - Retirement of Dr. Sabin, 1938
  - Rex, Richard O, 1933
  - Reznikoff, Paul, 1929-38
  - Rhea, Laurence J, 1937
  - Rhines, Chester, 1932
  - Rhoads, C P, 1932-39
  - Rich, Arnold R, 1933-40
  - Richards, Alfred Newton, 1923-40
  - Richardson, Henry B, 1927-28
  - Richter, Ina M, 1923-38
  - Richter, Maurice W, 1938
  - Ridge, Lola, 1941
  - Riesman, David, 1937
  - Riley, Henry Alsop, 1926-32
  - Rinehart, James F, 1931
  - Rioch, David, 1928-31
  - Rivers, Thomas M, 1937-38
  - Robb, J. M., 1930
  - Robb, Jane Sands, 1934
  - Robbins, Douglas F, 1936
  - Roberts, Edith A, 1940
  - Roberts, Kingsley, 1926-29
  - Robertson, Albert D, 1932-40
  - Robertson, David A, 1932-33
  - Robertson, O H, 1922-30
  - Robinovitch, L G, 1929
  - Robins, Rae, 1935
  - Robinson, G Canby, 1922-28
  - Robinson, Eulalia, 1932
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1930-37
  - Rockefeller Institute - Charge Sheets, 1939-40
  - Rockefeller Institute Publication Department, 1930
  - Rockefeller Institute - Reports, 1926-39
  - Rockefeller Institute - Staff Lists, 1925-36
  - Rockefeller Institute - Staff Meetings, 1932-40
  - Rockhill, Mrs. Charles S., 1931-33
  - Roderick, Lee M, 1927-28
  - Roerich, Museum, 1932
  - Rogers, Philip M, 1926
  - Rohrer, C W G, 1921
  - Rollhaus, P Edward, 1934
  - Roloff, Marjorie, 1937
  - Romanoff, Alexis L, 1931
  - Rosenbach, Abraham S W, 1933-34
  - Rosenberg, Norman, 1937
  - Rosenberger, Heinz, 1933
  - Rosenfeld, Jerome, 1943
  - Rosenthal, N, 1926-32
  - Rosett, Louise Carey, 1940
  - Ross, Margaret T, 1936
  - Ross, Vergil A, 1931
  - Rous, Peyton, 1924-40
  - Rowntree, L G, 1923
  - Rubenstein, I H, 1937
  - Ruderman, Louis M, 1932
  - Ruhrup, Helen E, 1931
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1940-43
  - Russell, Frederick F, 1928
  - Russell Sage College, 1938-44
  - Ruttan, R F, 1927
  - S, 1918-41
  - Sabin, F R - Theory of the Relation of the Teticulo-Endothelial System to Antibody Formation
  - Sabin, F R - Laboratory Report, 1933
  - Sabin, Mary S, 1932-37
  - Sachs, Ernest, 1930
  - Sacks, Benjamin, 1925-26
  - Sague, Mrs. Mary Landon, 1929
  - Saint George, A V, 1935
  - Sampson, John A, 1927-34
  - Sampson, Myra M, 1935
  - Sanford, Mrs. Val, 1937
  - Sanger, Margaret, 1932-34
  - Saunders, W L, 2nd, 1925
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A, 1935-38
  - Sayers, R R, 1933
  - Scarlo, Mrs. Frank, 1931
  - Schaefer, S W, 1935
  - Schaible, C E, 1931
  - Schain, Philip, 1943
  - Schleuder, Herbert W, 1932
  - Schlomovitz, B H, 1932
  - Schmidt, Louis B, 1932-34
  - Schmidt, William, 1939
  - Schrader, Sally Hughes, 1922
  - Schraeder, Charles R, 1937
  - Schram, Mildred W S, 1940
  - Schuyler, William M, 1926
  - Schweizer, Malvina, 1933
  - Schwimmer, Rosika, 1937
  - Science Service, 1933, 1937
  - Seastone, C. V., Jr., 1935
  - Seibert, Florence Barbara, 1928-45
  - Senior, H D, 1922-34
  - Seton, Grace T, 1935
  - Sewall, Henry, 1925-38
  - Sewall, Henry - The Skin as an Organ of Experimental, n.d.
  - Shaffer, Philip A, 1931
  - Sharpe, John C, 1935
  - Shaw, Mrs. Walter F, 1938
  - Shayeson, Francine, 1932
  - Sheldon, Edward, 1935-37
  - Sheldon, Mrs. Mary S, 1925
  - Sheldon, Paul B, 1936
  - Sherwood, Margaret, 1935-36
  - Sherwood, Marion B, 1926-27
  - Sherwood, Mary, 1924, 1935
  - Shields, Randolph T, 1922-36
  - Shimer, William A, 1936
  - Shope, Richard E, 1928, 1935
  - Shouse, Catherine Filene, 1933
  - Shull, E C, 1922
  - Sigerist, H E, 1931-33
  - Sigma Delta Epsilon, 1926-30
  - Sigma Xi, 1927, 1939
  - Sills, Kenneth, 1930-31
  - Silver, Rose, 1932
  - Simmonds, Nina, 1936
  - Simmons, W W, 1933
  - Simms, Henry S, 1942
  - Simonton, Willetta E, 1931
  - Simpson, Augusta, 1930
  - Simpson, Ethel D, 1928
  - Singer, Edward, 1934
  - Small, Mary Louise, 1926
  - Smith, Adelaide Ross, 1928
  - Smith, Arthur H, 1930
  - Smith, Carl H, 1933, 1939
  - Smith, Christianna, 1926-38
  - Smith College, 1940-42
  - Smith College Alumnae Quarterly, 1934-38
  - Smith College Club, 1920-37
  - Smith David T, 1925-44
  - Smith, Edric B, 1924-36
  - Smith, George H, 1924
  - Smith, Hilton A, 1940
  - Smith, Jessica, 1937
  - Smith, Mary B, 1938
  - Smith, Maurice I, 1931-34
  - Smith, Philip E, 1936
  - Smith, Sybil L, 1932
  - Smith, Theobald, 1935
  - Smithburn, Kenneth C, 1931-46
  - Smithburn, Kenneth C. - Bibliography, n.d.
  - Smyth, Francis Scott, 1935
  - Snapper, I, 1932
  - Snow, Rosamond Dean, 1937
  - Societies - Miscellaneous, n.d.
  - Society for Experimental Biology And Medicine, 1929-40
  - Solingen, Germany, 1933
  - Soper, Willard B, 1933
  - Soule, Malcolm H, 1837-38
  - Spaltro, Arnaldo, 1935
  - Speakman, Edward T, 1930
  - Spencer Lens Company, 1923-35
  - Spies, Tom D, 1935
  - Spitz, Sophie, 1934
  - Sponer, Hertha, 1934
  - Spooner, Florence, 1933
  - Sporborg, Constance, 1936
  - Squier, George O, 1933
  - Squier, Raymond R, 1922
  - Stains #1 -Borguist -Coleman & Bell Company, n.d.
  - Stains #2 -H J Conn, n.d.
  - Stains #3 -Ehrlich-Wright, n.d.
  - Stanley, George E, 1933
  - Stanley-Brown, M, 1932
  - Stark, Naomi A, 1932
  - Stearns, Genevieve, 1937
  - Stearns, Robert L, 1930, 1937
  - Steele, Brandt F, 1933
  - Steensland, H S, 1924
  - Stein, Marguerite Theiss, 1932-46
  - Stephens, Arthur R, 1937
  - Stetler, Anna C, 1936
  - Stewart, Elizabeth C, 1936, n.d.
  - Stifel, John L, 1925
  - Stilwell, Helen Barton, 1936
  - Stobie, William, 1930
  - Stockard, Charles R, 1923, 1933-34
  - Stokes, William H, 1936
  - Stoop, R, 1932
  - Storey, W Edward, 1933
  - Stowdon [?], Elizabeth, 1916-17
  - Stratman-Thomas, Warren, 1936, 1940, n.d.
  - Streeter, George L, 1925-43
  - Strong, Gordon, 1924-38
  - Studholme, J M, 1933
  - Sturgis, Cyrus C., 1928
  - Sturtevant, E H, 1936
  - Sugiyama, S, 1925-40
  - Sugiyama, S - The Developement of the Blood-Cells in the Vascular..., n.d.
  - Sumwalt, Florence Edwards, 1935-40
  - Supravital Staining, 1928-36
  - Sure, Barnett, 1927
  - Sutton, Alan C, 1919
  - Swain, Carla, 1935-37
  - Swain, Henry II, 1932-38
  - Sweany, Henry C, 1935-36
  - Swett, Frank H, 1925-36
  - Swift, Homer F, 1934-39
  - Swift, Walker E, 1933
  - Sydenstricker, V P, 1933-35
  - Syphus, Clara M, 1930
  - T, 1922-45
  - Tait, John, 1926
  - Tappan, Vivian, 1926-40
  - Taussig, Helen B, 1925-36
  - Taylor, Bliss, 1934
  - Taylor, E W, 1900
  - Taylor, Harry B, 1935
  - Technique, 1923-32, n.d.
  - Ten Broeck, Carl, 1922-36
  - Tesar, Walter, 1938
  - Thau, Morris, 1931
  - Thayer, William S, 1926-33
  - Thomas Nelson & Sons, 1932
  - Thomas, M Carey, 1922-35
  - Thomas, M Carey Prize, 1935-37
  - Thomas, Robert M, 1932-39
  - Thompson, William P, 1930-36
  - Thompson, Mrs. W R, 1928
  - Thuringer, Joseph M, 1931
  - Thorne, Mary, 1924-25
  - Tillett, William S, 1926-38
  - Time, 1941
  - Titcomb, Lillian Ray, 1929
  - Tompkins, Edna H, 1939
  - Tonolla, E Howard, 1937
  - Torrance, Charles C, 1933
  - Total Counts, 1924-25, n.d.
  - Town Hall Club, 1934
  - Tracy, Martha, 1922-32
  - Traut, Herbert F, 1925-38
  - Trimble, Andrew, 1929-31
  - Troutman, Pauline, 1938
  - Trudeau Award, 1945
  - Tuberculosis - Monograph, requests, n.d.
  - Tuberculosis - Letters Regarding A-Z, n.d.
  - Tuberculosis Publicity, n.d.
  - Tuberculosis Sanitarium, Chicago, 1932
  - Tuberculosis Sanitarium Conference of Metropolitan New York, 1935
  - Tully, Marion, 1931
  - U, 1931-35
  - Uhlenhuth, Eduard, 1925, 1937
  - Unanswered Letters, 1925-36
  - United States Constitution Sesquicentennial Dinner, 1937
  - United States. Department of State - General Advisory Committee, 1934-44
  - United States Office of War Information, 1945
  - United States Society, 1933
  - United States Treasury Department, 1930
  - United States Weather Bureau, 1930
  - University in Exile - The New School for Social Research, 1935-38
  - University of Colorado, 1935
  - University of Michigan, 1926-37
  - Upham, J H J, 1931
  - Urey, Harold C, 1939
  - Ursini, Mrs. Carlotta, 1929
  - V, 1928-39
  - Valentine, Eleanor, 1934
  - Vanderlip, Narcissa, 1936
  - Van Der Stricht, Omer, 1919-25
  - Van Hoosen, Bertha, 1927-37
  - Van Slyke, Donald Dexter, 1934-41
  - Van Wesep, H B, 1941
  - Van Winkle, Charlotte, 1928-35
  - Vassar College, 1919-40
  - Vastola, A P, 1930-31
  - Vendel, S N, 1935
  - Vivisection, 1932
  - Von Kleinsmid, R B, 1935
  - W, 1919-39
  - Wade, H W, 1940-41
  - Wager, Martha, 1931
  - Waiss, A S, 1932
  - Wald, Lillian D, 1936
  - Walker, Alyce M, 1937
  - Walker, George, 1925
  - Walker, Helen Adele, 1937
  - Wall, Alma S, 1935-36
  - Wall, Margaret J, 1935
  - Wallace, George Barclay, 1915-37
  - Wallhauser, Andrew, 1931
  - Walter, W, 1925
  - Walters, Mary Jane, 1931-32
  - Warburg, Bettina, 1931
  - Warburg, Paul Felix, 1934
  - Ward, Grant E, 1923, 1933
  - Ward, Henry Baldwin, 1916, 1921
  - Warfield, E D, 1933
  - Waring, James J, 1928-45
  - Warm Box, n.d.
  - Warren, Shields, 1936
  - Washburn, Margaret Floy, 1931, 1939
  - Wastl, Helene, 1936-38
  - Waters, Campbell E, 1938
  - Watkins, C H, 1930
  - Watkins, C J, 1936
  - Watson, Goodwin, 1938
  - Waugh, Thomas, 1923
  - Waverly Press Incorporated, 1925, 1932
  - Waxman, Percy, 1930
  - Weaner, Agnes Rice, 1935
  - Wearn, Joseph T, 1922-33
  - Webb, Gerald B, 1931-40
  - Webb, Robert Alexander, 1927-33
  - Webster, Bruce, 1935-38
  - Webster, Leslie T, 1934-36
  - Weed, Lewis H, 1924-38
  - Weier, Karl, 1927-29
  - Weier, T Elliot, 1932
  - Weimer, Dolores E, 1935
  - Weiskotten, H G, 1924, 1934
  - Weiss, Charles, 1934-38
  - Welch, William Henry, 1932-34
  - Wells, Arthur H, 1936
  - Wells, Cliford H, 1921-26
  - Wells, Herbert S, 1922
  - Welsh, Lilian, 1924-38
  - Wertheimer, Mildred, 1935
  - Wesson, Miley B, 1930, 1939
  - West, Randolph, 1928-34
  - Westerman, May C W, 1936
  - Wetzel, Norman C, 1926
  - Weyl, Hermann, 1938
  - Wharton, Lawrence R, 1927-28
  - Whipple, George Hoyt, 1926-37
  - Whipple, Allen O, 1926
  - White, Earlene, 1939
  - White, Mrs. H. V, 1932
  - White, James T., Company, 1925
  - White, William Charles, 1924-45
  - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection, 1929-32
  - Whitehill, Clara A, 1932
  - Whitmoyer, R B, 1934
  - Who's Who, 1923-36
  - Wick, Frances G, 1933
  - Wiedmann, Floyd E, 1935
  - Wilder, Harris Hawthorne, 1925
  - Wilkens, Elizabeth M Reese, 1925-28
  - Wilkins, Ernest H, 1937
  - Williams, Etta, 1930
  - Williams, Florence V, 1937
  - Williams, J Whitridge, 1923
  - Williams, Lou, 1937
  - Williams and Wilkins Company, 1925-38
  - Willis, H S, 1931
  - Willson, Winifred, 1935
  - Wilson, D Wright, 1925-26
  - Wilson, Edmund Beecher, 1941
  - Wilson, George W, 1931
  - Wilson, Grace, 1936
  - Wilson, Helen C, 1922, 1936
  - Wilson, Louis B, 1923
  - Wilson College, 1933-39
  - Winn, William A, 1934
  - Winterntiz, Milton C, 1919-38
  - Wiseman, Bruce K, 1930-39
  - Wislocki, Florence Clothier, 1936
  - Wislocki, George B, 1925-42
  - Wistar Institute, 1923-36
  - Wiswell, Jean, 1934
  - Wittke, Carl F, 1943
  - Wolfe, Harold R, 1939-40